nypress.com 2019-12-14

# Straus News

We are committed to protecting consumer privacy online.  The purpose of our policy is to inform you about the types of information we gather about you when you visit strausnews.com or any of its sister sites, which include but are not limited to advertisernewsnorth.com, advertisernewssouth.com, spartaindependent.com, townshipjournal.com, warwickadvertiser.com, thephoto-news.com, chroniclenewspaper.com, westmilfordmessenger.com, pikecountycourier.com, nypress.com, ourtownny.com, westsidespirit.com, otdowntown.com, chelseaclintonnews.com, and dirt-mag.com (collectively, the “Straus News Sites”).  The policy also describes how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct, that information.

**_How You Accept This Policy_**  
By visiting any of the Straus News Sites, or by otherwise providing us with personally identifiable information (such as an email address), you agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy.

**_How We Gather Information from Users_**  
How we collect and store information depends on the page you are visiting, the activities in which you elect to participate, and the services provided.  You can visit some pages on the Straus News Sites without affirmatively providing any information.  Other pages may prompt you to provide information, such as when you submit a press release, business milestone, letter to the editor, or a photo to a Straus News Site. You may also provide information when you participate in sweepstakes and contests, voting and polling activities, photo galleries, message boards, and other areas of the Straus News Sites.  
When you submit any of the above information, we may collect personal information (“PI”), such your first name and last name, address, or email address, which you choose to provide to us.    We may collect PI if you contact us or otherwise give it to us (e.g., in an email).

Like most websites, we also collect information automatically and through the use of electronic tools that may not be transparent to our visitors. We may collect information about the computer, mobile telephone, smart phone, tablet computer, or other device you use to access Straus News.  For example, we may log the name of your Internet Service Provider or use “cookie” technology. Among other things, the cookie may store your user name and password, sparing you from having to re-enter that information each time you visit, or may control the number of times you encounter a particular advertisement while visiting the Site.  As we adopt additional technology, we may also gather information through other means.  In certain cases, you can choose not to provide us with information, for example by setting your browser to refuse to accept cookies, but doing so may inhibit the Straus News Sites’ functionality.

**_What We Do With The Non-Personally Identifiable Information We Collect_**  
We may use information that is not personally identifiable to enhance the visitor experience of the Straus News Sites, to operate and maintain the Straus News Sites, to investigate and understand how the Straus News Sites are used, to monitor and protect the security and integrity of the Straus News Sites, and to analyze our business.  As one example, we may combine information about your usage patterns with similar information obtained from other users to learn which pages are visited most or what features are most attractive.  Aggregated information may occasionally be shared with our advertisers and business partners, but cannot be used to contact you individually.

**_How We Use And Disclose PI_**  
We may use PI to email you or to otherwise communicate with you about activities relating to the Straus News Sites and our business, including marketing and promotion.  You can opt out of receiving future promotional and advertising related emails and electronic communications by following the unsubscribe link in any such emails.

We may use PI to enhance the visitor experience of the Straus News Sites, to operate and maintain the Straus News Sites, to investigate and understand how our Service are used, to analyze our business, and to monitor and protect the security and integrity of the Straus New Sites.

We may disclose PI as required by law or in response to service of legal process, such as a court order, summons, subpoena, or the like. 

We may share PI with trusted partners who provide services related to the Straus News Sites (such as website hosting).  These trusted partners do not have the right to use this PI for any purpose other than those related to the Straus New Sites.  
Information about our users, including PI, may be disclosed or transferred to entities now or in the future affiliated with us or as part of any merger, acquisition, change of control, debt financing, insolvency, bankruptcy or sale of our assets, and may be used in the businesses of any entity so receiving it. 

Although we do not do so now, we may aggregate your PI with that of other users and sell it to third parties. 

**_What Information We Do Not Collect_**  
When you share or recommend articles or content from any Straus News Site on Facebook, Twitter, or any other third-party social media platform, that action is governed by the third-party site’s respective privacy policy.  We do not track or store a record of those comments or actions, and you should take care to review the third-party’s privacy policy before sharing any such content.

Moreover, Straus News does not knowingly collect or solicit personally identifiable information from or about children under the age of 13.  If we discover we have received any information from a child under the age of 13 in violation of this policy, we will delete that information immediately. If you believe, the Straus News Sites have any information from or about anyone under the age of 13, please contact us at webmanager@strausnews.com.  Children under the age of 13 are specifically prohibited from registering as Members of strausnews.com.

**_Affiliated Sites, Linked Sites And Advertisements_**  
Straus News expects its partners, advertisers, and third-party affiliates to respect the privacy of our users.  However, third parties, including our partners, advertisers, affiliates, and other content providers accessible through our site, may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices.  For example, during your visit to the Straus News Sites you may follow a link to, or view as part of a frame on a Straus News Site, certain content that is actually created or hosted by a third party.  Also, through the Straus News Sites you may be introduced to, or be able to access, information, websites, advertisements, features, contests, or sweepstakes offered by other parties.  Straus News is not responsible for the actions or policies of such third parties.

While on our site, our advertisers, promotional partners, or other third parties may use cookies or other technology to attempt to identify some of your preferences or retrieve information about you.  For example, some of our advertising may be served by third parties and may include cookies that enable the advertiser to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before.  Through features available on our site, third parties may use cookies or other technology to gather information.  Straus News does not control the use of this technology or the resulting information and is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties.

Please be careful and responsible whenever you are online. Should you choose to voluntarily disclose personally identifiable information in public areas on the Site, such as in message boards, chat areas or in advertising or notices you post, that information can be viewed publicly and can be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge and may result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of Strausnews.com and this policy.

**_How Do I Opt-Out or Correct Information About Me_**  
You may always opt-out of receiving future e-mail messages and newsletters from Straus News.  We provide you with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about you.  To do so, you can send us a message at webmanager@strausnews.com. 

**_Data Security_**  
We do our best to preserve the integrity and security of your PI.  We cannot, however, ensure the security of any information you transmit to the Service, and you do so at your own risk.  Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing or by emailing us at webmanager@strausnews.com.

**_International Visitors_**  
This Service is hosted in the United States.  If you are an international visitor, you should note that by providing your PI, you are:  (i) permitting the transfer of your PI to the United States which may not have the same data protection laws as the country in which you reside; and (ii) permitting the use of your PI in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**_Changes to this policy_**  
If we make any changes to this policy, we will post such changes on this page.  Such changes shall become effective immediately upon posting and, unless provided otherwise, will not apply retroactively.  If we make any material changes and you have provided us with an e-mail address, we will do our best to notify you of any such changes. 

**_Contact_**  
Please contact use with any questions you may have at webmanager@strausnews.com, (845) 469-9000, or at the below address:

Straus News  
20 West Avenue  
Chester, NY 10918-1053  
(845) 469-9000
